It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
Positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's a family guy
Peter, thanks a lot
for having us out on your boat.
- No problem.
- Peter, are you sure Santos and Pasqual...
don't mind coming in on a Saturday
to serve us drinks?
Are you kidding, Lois? They're Portuguese.
Work is their cocaine.
Besides, look at them in their tuxedos.
They look like little people.
Hey, Meg. What's going on?
What's going on? You having a good time?
Yeah, no, I'm having a good time.
Hey, what's going on?
Listen, you're 17 now, right?
I was just throwing it out there.
I was thinking, you know,
if you ever want to...
I don't know, screw around or something.
Hey, Joe.
So, you know, it's just something to mull
around in the old noggin.
Damn. What is it about golf
that always brings out the worst in me?
So, Annika Sorenstam,
you're quite the female golfer, aren't you?
Yes, quite the female golfer.
I knew it! Look! Everybody, look! Look!
She's a fraud!
All right, I caught a fish!
Sorry about that, Loretta.
Hey, can I have my fish back?
You're gonna have to reach
into the cookie jar.
Well, I can't just...
You're my best friend's wife.
Reach into... All right!
Yeah, you go in and get that.
Show that fishy who's boss.
Loretta, they have some of that
three-bean salad you're so fond of.
Hey, Quagmire.
Well, we'll have to do this
again sometime.
You name the time and the place,
little neck.
I've always loved charades.
- Your turn, Joe.
- The category is Famous People.
- Okay, guess who I am.
- Ironside!
- Larry Flynt!
- Stephen Hawking!
- Dr. Strangelove!
- Roy Campanella!
- Richard Petty!
- Lance Armstrong!
Neil Armstrong! Stretch Armstrong!
Stretch Cunningham!
Howard Cunningham! Potsie Weber!
Natalie Wood. Definitely Natalie Wood.
- Somebody save him, he can't swim!
- He's not even kicking.
- Kick, Joe, kick!
- Peter, he's a paraplegic.
That doesn't mean he can't hear.
Kick, Joe, kick!
Somebody help him!
Gay!
You were right, Peter.
It was Natalie Wood.
Lois, why the hell do we have to
take a stupid CPR class?
Because, Peter, none of us knew
what to do when Joe was drowning.
Now, be quiet and pay attention.
Hi, there. I'd like to welcome you all
to CPR.
I see a lot of smiles here in this room.
There's one. There's another.
That's good.
I see that soda up under your chair.
That's all right.
Soda's all right on my watch.
We also got Oreos here and fresh coffee.
Everybody likes a snack.
Now, who wants to go first?
No takers? Well, fine. I'll go first.
Peter, why don't you volunteer?
No, I don't volunteer for anything
since I helped those guys...
repaint the Sistine Chapel.
Listen, I thought the stuff that was there
was kind of lame. So I put this up.
I figured Andre the Giant
would be a little hipper.
Get back some of those boys
you scared away.
And that's pretty much all there is to it.
It's hard, jagged, and tastes like alcohol.
Just like kissing Faye Dunaway.
Easy now.
I can't believe we just did that.
But, you know, that stuff about
spending the day together tomorrow...
I forgot. Actually, I have a thing.
But, you know,
you have my e-mail address.
So drop me a line. And then I'll have yours.
And we'll take it from there. So...
Bellybutton.
Well, I'll see you later.
So, it's official.
Y'all are card-carrying lifesavers.
Holy crap, a card with my name on it!
I am now Peter Griffin, certified CPR.
Come on, Lois! I've got lives to save.
Thanks. Be safe.
Nobody had any of the coffee.
Only a couple of Oreos gone.
I'm gonna take the rest home to the cats.
Sorry, I was dialing the phone.
Are you all right?
Don't worry about it.
Doesn't look like there's any...
Peter Griffin, certified CPR.
Don't anyone panic!
- What the hell are you doing?
- You know, I don't think he's hurt.
I'll get to you in a moment, sir.
I'm gonna have to check...
and see if he soiled himself.
- Sir? Sir?
- What the hell is wrong with you?
- I've got to check if you've soiled yourself.
- Get off of me. Are you crazy?
Sir? I'm gonna need you
to stop struggling, all right?
- Leave him alone.
- I hurt my elbow!
- I've got to get these trousers off.
- Somebody call the cops!
- I gotta see if you soiled yourself.
- Nobody asked you to get involved!
Get off him, you jackass!
I'm gonna need you to step back. All right,
Looks like we're clean down here.
You guys take it easy. No need to
thank me. Just pay it forward.
- So they revoked your CPR card, huh?
- Yeah.
This is worse than
when they took away my library card...
for reading while intoxicated.
Don't be ashamed of your hand,
Johnny Tremain.
You still live in exciting times.
Crap!
Sir, do you know how loud
you were reading?
"The life of a silversmith's apprentice
was not an easy one!"
I got to figure out some way
to get that card back.
You could always take the class again.
I mean, I'm sure they'd give you
another card.
[Screaming]
- Hey, do you hear that?
- What?
Sounds like someone screaming.
What is it, boy?
What are you trying to say?
It sounds like Loretta is screaming.
- Trouble at the old mill?
- What are you, insane?
- Somebody fall through the ice?
- It's summer.
- Bobcat?
- [Barking]
Loretta's in trouble? Come on, boy!
Peter Griffin,
temporarily suspended CPR...
- Holy crap!
- We should go.
Boy, that was embarrassing, huh?
Walking in on Loretta and Cleveland
having sex.
- Peter, that wasn't...
- You know, for a large, heavyset...
black guy,
Cleveland's got a cute, little white ass.
That wasn't Cleveland.
It was some white guy.
- What was that?
- Shut up and put some more...
of that sugar in my bowl.
Wait a minute. Brian? If that wasn't
Cleveland doing it with Loretta...
then Loretta's having an affair.
We can't tell anyone about this.
That is the last thing in the world
we want to do.
What a day!
We've done everything in the world.
So I guess the only thing left to do...
is tell you that Loretta Brown
is having an affair.
- Good Lord!
- Oh, no!
Oh, God! I'm screwed.
This is worse than that time
I had to fess up to the nation.
My fellow Americans,
I have not been entirely truthful with you.
I did ga-googity that girl.
I ga-shmoigedied her ga-flavety
with my googus.
And I am sorry.
Yeah, any idea who it was, Peter?
No, we didn't see his face.
All we know is it's a skinny white guy...
with a tattoo on his left butt cheek.
Well, I better tell Cleveland.
I got a knack for delivering bad news.
I don't know how to tell you this,
Mr. DeVanney.
So I'll let these guys do it.
[Singing] You have AIDS
Yes, you have AIDS
I hate to tell you, boy, that you have AIDS
You've got the AIDS
You may have caught it
when you stuck that filthy needle in here
Or maybe all that unprotected sex
put you here
It isn't clear
But what we're certain of is you have AIDS
Yes, you have AIDS
Not HIV, but full-blown AIDS
Be sure that you see
That this is not HIV
But full-blown AIDS
Not HIV, but really
Full-blown AIDS
I'm sorry
I wish it was something less serious.
But it's AIDS
You've got the AIDS
So, listen, Cleveland.
The reason I asked you out here...
I've been wanting to talk to you
about something.
In Superman II, what is the story
with that cellophane "S"...
that Superman rips off his chest
and throws at the bad guy?
Prepare to be destroyed, Superman!
- What was that?
- Yeah, take that, you jerk.
- That was a minor inconvenience.
- Yeah, well, that's the idea.
- Slowed you down.
- I'll say. Ow.
- Didn't see that coming, did you?
- No.
Yeah, well, you know, take that.
Which actually brings me
to my next point:
- Your wife's cheating on you.
- What?
Yeah, it's actually a pretty funny story,
true story.
Brian and I walked into your house
and she was with some guy going...
Bam, bam, bam.
- Peter, maybe...
- Hang on, I'm not done.
Bam, bam.
And then she's all, "Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah."
Bam, bam, bam.
You want to take it
from here, Bamm-Bamm?
Bam-bam, bam-bam.
- You want to take it from here, Emeril?
- Bam!
So that's what we're dealing with here.
Any thoughts?
Loretta, is it true what they're saying?
Were you really having carnal relations
with another gentleman?
I'm a woman, Cleveland.
I need some passion in my life.
I need a real man.
And Lord knows that ain't you.
Well, I admit after a long day at work,
I don't always come home...
with that "Riunite on ice,
that's nice" mentality.
And for that, I apologize.
Apologize? I cheat on you
and you apologize to me?
Cleveland Brown, you are pathetic!
I disagree, but I respect your candor.
Goodbye, Cleveland.
I love you.
[Doorbell ringing]
Hi, Cleveland.
- Hey, what are you doing here?
- Loretta kicked me out.
Cleveland, I am so sorry.
You can stay here as long as you like.
Cleveland, sit down.
I want to sing a little song
that kept me going when I had troubles.
[Playing Rock Lobster by the B-52's]
[Singing]
We were at the beach
Everybody had matching towels
Somebody went under a dock
And there they saw a rock
But it wasn't a rock
It was a rock lobster
Rock lobster
Yeah, you're gonna be okay.
Now, everybody, Cleveland's gonna be
staying with us for a few days.
That's right, kids.
So just treat him like one of the family.
You mean like Cousin Janine who we're
polite to but then mock her diabetes...
on the drive home?
She can't eat caramel.
Exactly.
Can I touch your hair?
I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna touch it.
It's like a sheep!
You know, Peter,
I'm a little worried about Cleveland.
His wife cheated on him,
kicked him out of the house...
and he doesn't seem at all affected by it.
He's probably bottling up his emotions.
That's not good for you.
Right. I almost got an ulcer
after you shelled out $200...
for tickets to Crossing Over
with John Edward.
I'm sensing an "A."
Does your name begin with an "A"?
- No.
- A "B"?
- C, D, E, F, G, H, I, J, K, L, M, N, O, P?
- "P"! Peter! My name's Peter!
- Is your name Peter?
Wow, you are some kind of sorcerer.
What Cleveland really needs right now
is to learn how to express his feelings.
Now, what he needs right now
is a revenge lay.
And I know just who to talk to.
[Doorbell ringing]
- Oh, God!
- Sorry, guys. Let me throw something on.
- Peter, look!
- Holy crap, that's the tattoo!
Well, I think we're about to find out
who the culprit is.
5-5-5-0-1-4-3.
- Peter, l...
- Shut up, Brian! I'm sleuthing.
[Phone ringing]
- Hello?
- Quagmire?
- Yeah.
- Hey, it's Peter.
What's going on, buddy?
We're at your house.
Peter, he's the one we saw
sleeping with Loretta!
Oh, my God!
Damn it, I knew this was gonna happen!
I didn't mean it, you know?
I knew it was a mistake!
It never felt right!
Please don't tell Cleveland!
Well, all right, Quagmire.
Cleveland, Quagmire's sleeping
with your wife!
- What?
- Quagmire slept with Loretta?
Oh, my God, Cleveland! I am so sorry.
I can only imagine
what you must be feeling right now.
It's okay.
It's okay? It's okay to be betrayed
by your wife and best friend?
Better it be Quagmire than someone
she could get a disease from.
Cleveland, don't you see?
This is why your wife left you.
You don't have any passion.
Sometimes a woman wants to see
her man be a man.
You got to push back a little!
You got to get a little rough!
Oh, God! Peter, hit me!
Yeah!
Wow, so that's something,
about Quagmire and Loretta, huh?
Cleveland, we got to get
your manhood back.
Now, the first thing we're gonna do...
is take you to a good, old-fashioned,
wrestling match.
All right, Cleveland.
Nothing like a good smackdown...
to get the testosterone going.
I must be in Quahog
'cause all I see is a bunch of hicks!
You take that back,
Macho Man Randy Savage!
Doesn't he make you so mad you just...
- want to go down there and hit him?
- No.
Well, maybe not him
'cause he's kind of big.
But don't you want to hit the guy
sitting next to you?
Not him 'cause he's kind of big, too.
But don't you want to hit his kid?
Take that, Macho Man Randy Savage.
You jerk.
All right, Cleveland. If this doesn't
light a fire in your belly, nothing will.
Hey, look at me. I'm Quagmire.
I had sex with your wife.
Those are so his mannerisms.
- Peter, what the hell are you doing?
- I'm not Peter, I'm Quagmire.
- And I'm doing you, Loretta.
- What the hell?
- You like that? Yeah.
- Hey!
- Much better than Cleveland.
- Peter, knock it off!
- Get you damn hands off me...
- You like it dirty, don't you?
What the hell are you doing?
What is that in your pocket?
- Lois! Somebody!
- Quagmire's got you. Yeah.
Glenn Quagmire, you're dead!
[Theme music from Popeye]
All right, calm down, Cleveland.
I'm gonna kill Quagmire!
Oh, God, you're hyperventilating!
Chris, get me a bag.
Okay, Cleveland, breathe into the bag.
It'll calm you down.
- Peter, I'm not sure that that's...
- Not now, Lois!
Okay, Cleveland, Cleveland,
relax, relax, relax.
Relax, relax.
There you go. There you go. Okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
- It's all gonna be okay.
- Peter, you better do your CPR.
There's no time. I got to go warn
Quagmire while I got the chance.
Quick, to the Peter copter!
[Peter screaming]
Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, my God!
- Peter, what the hell?
- Joe, get inside!
- The blades are still spinning!
- Oh, my God, Peter! What is that thing?
- Joe! Get inside!
- It's tearing up my yard!
- Oh, my God!
- No!
- Joe, I am sorry, buddy.
- It's okay. Look, it's okay.
- Are you okay? You all right?
- It's okay. I'm fine.
- Everybody's fine.
- That was scary.
- Peter, what are we doing here?
- Trust me, Quagmire.
Cleveland will never think to look
for you at Mayor West's house.
- Hey, there.
- How you doing?
Good evening, gentlemen.
Listen, Mayor West,
my friend Quagmire here's in trouble.
- He needs a place to stay tonight.
- Say no more. I'll protect you, sir.
It is my job. I only ask
that you do not feed my cat, Bootsie...
as he's already eaten and might throw up.
Well, Derwood, now you really are
the big man of the house.
Mother, change him back.
You know, Endora,
I'm getting a little sick of this crap.
You ever seen one of these? Huh?
You know what this is? Huh?
- No!
- Yeah, it's holy water. Huh? Yeah.
Try it. How's that feel?
You like that?
Power of Christ compels you, bitch.
I hate Bewitched.
Hey, so that's a pretty
reasonable reaction, huh?
It's all right to go to sleep, my friend.
I'll stand guard.
Okay.
Don't worry. I'll be here all night.
Just don't try to make me smile.
I'm forbidden to smile.
Oh, no.
That episode of Growing Pains
when Mike's friend Boner...
ran for student council.
Boner.
His name was Boner.
- I've failed you.
- This is kind of creeping me out.
- I'm gonna go.
- Take this, for protection.
What the hell's this for?
When the time comes, you'll know.
I'll teach him to mess with my wife.
Hi, Cleveland.
Will you be joining us for dinner?
[Cleveland growls]
- Okay, then.
- He's a Rocky machine!
Peter, we have got to do something
about Cleveland.
I think you created a monster.
Well, there's only one thing to do, Lois.
We've got to get
Loretta and Cleveland back together.
And I know just how to do it.
To the Hinden-Peter!
JOE: Oh, my God!
PETER: Joe, I am so sorry.
How can you afford these things?
[Answering machine beeping]
Yeah, Cleveland, this is Quagmire.
Listen, I feel awful.
Why don't you come on over and we can...
try to get things back
to the way they used to be?
Remember how it was?
[In pseudo-Czech accent] Perhaps here
there are many unsuspecting foxes...
to have sex with us.
[In pseudo-Czech accent] That is why
we wear tight pants to show our bulges.
- We are two wild and crazy guys!
- Two wild and crazy guys!
You guys look stupid.
Anyway, let's talk this thing through.
Hey, Cleveland.
I was just leaving you a message.
You violated the sanctity of my marriage.
When the time comes, you'll know.
QUAGMIRE: Damn it!
This is awful!
Somebody stop them! Do something!
Good. Let the hate flow through you.
You're not helping!
I can't.
It isn't in me to cause harm to anyone.
No matter how much
someone has harmed me.
I'm sorry, Cleveland.
Cleveland, I think this beautiful woman
would like to say something to you.
You told me this was Lois' intervention.
- Nice. Cleveland?
- Loretta, what you did was unforgivable.
- This marriage is over.
- Well, that's just fine, Cleveland.
'Cause I am through being your wife.
Well, I may not be perfect,
but I deserve better than you.
Look at that, Lois.
As beautiful as an HBO minority fairytale.
But, Peter, their marriage is ending.
Look at the bright side, Lois.
It's a chance for a fresh start
for both Cleveland and...
[Audience applauding]
Oh, my God!
What are you doing?
- What's wrong with you?
- What the hell, man?
- Hurts, doesn't it?
- What the hell... Yes!
What the hell's your problem?
- My friend? My friend?
- What?
- You've been kicked in the...
- No way!
- You're gonna be on TV.
- Oh, sweet!
- Oh, my God.
- Wow! We love that show.
- That is awesome. Hey, hi.
- You're on it.
Oh, wow.
Glenn, you sure you want to do this?
I already told you I forgive you.
- No, I feel like I got off too easy.
- All right. If you insist.
- You wanna ring the bell, Apollo?
- All right.
Ding, ding.
[Theme from Rocky III playing]
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru